<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InnovationTraining</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_home_page2">HomePage2</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="title_activity_topic_page">TopicPage</string>

    <string name="title_activity_congrats_page">CongratsPage</string>

    <string name="title_activity_keepers_page">KeepersPage</string>

    <string name="title_activity_progress_page">ProgressPage</string>

    <string name="title_activity_reminder_page">ReminderPage</string>

    <string name="title_activity_faq">faq</string>
    <string name="Home_Page2_Options">Loading Topic of the Day...</string>
    <string name="stringthing">Next</string>
    <string name="parag">1. Choose between the provided topic and your own topic (it can be anything).
    \n2. Enter 10 ideas about that topic.
    \n3. Notice as your creativity increases-you should see it improve in 3-6 months.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_topic">NewTopic</string>

    <string name="faq_menu">FAQ</string>
    <string name="new_topic_menu">New Topic</string>
    <string-array name="inspirationalMessages">
        <item>Good job!</item>
        <item>Great job!</item>
        <item>Fantastic job!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="topicsOfTheDay">
        <item>How to create flourless pancakes</item>
        <item>How to reduce food waste in restaurants</item>
        <item>How to reduce food waste in your home</item>
        <item>How to get kids to put away technology at the dinner table</item>
        <item>Situations that are appropriate to bribe children</item>
        <item>How to get young people to vote</item>
        <item>Alternatives to traditional political debates</item>
        <item>Ways you could get involved with local politics</item>
        <item>Methods of keeping students off mobile phones in school</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">Splash</string>

    <string name="faq">
<![CDATA[
<h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2><br>
<b>How to use the app?</b>

<p>Using the app is simple. Once per day 1) open the app; 2) take a look at the topic of the day and decide if

you want to use that topic or choose your own topic—anything you want to think about is OK; 3) enter

ten ideas about that topic—it usually gets challenging around idea number five; 4) click the done button;

5) and that’s it—just do this every day and your innovation or creativity should increase in 3-6 months.</p>

<b>I want to save my ideas, how do I do that?</b>

<p>The idea of the app is to increase your creativity and innovation. Its not designed to be a record of your

ideas. If an idea is really great you will remember it. All of the others—just jot them down in the app and

let them go. It is about the process not the ideas you come up with.</p>

<b>What if I don’t like your topic?</b>

<p>No problem, if you don’t like the topic of the day just come up with your own topic. Coming up with a

topic of the day that relates to your life and interests is also a great way to improve your creativity.</p>

<b>What is the concept behind this app?</b>

<p>There is a theory that you can develop more innovation and creativity by training your brain—your brain

and the neurological connections for creativity can be exercised like a muscle. There are several

methods for helping your brain become creatively stronger. This app is based upon an idea made

popular by James Altucher. He posits that by doing some simple things each day you will increase

creativity, and one of those is to write down 10 ideas on a single topic every day. It doesn’t matter what

the idea or topic is—it can be anything from making a better tennis racquet to how to improve solar

panels. Ten ideas is key though as any fewer doesn’t stretch the creative muscle. It is not intended that

the ideas be looked at again necessarily as the purpose isn’t to come up with a good idea, but rather to

have developed thousands of ideas over time. The goal of this app is to simplify this process, making it

easy to complete the exercise every day. The app will prompt you to complete the exercise, provide you

with a topic if necessary, and provide you space to enter the 10 ideas.</p>

<b>Why did you create this app?</b>

<p>It’s simple. We are all about creativity and wanted to do this exercise. But we found it challenging to

remember to do it every day without a reminder and it became tiresome coming up with new topics.

We knew it could be made easier and an app like this would help us stick with the daily exercise for the

six months.</p>

<b>Who created this app?</b>

<p>This app was programmed by Devika Kumar for dfusion. dfusion (http://www.dfusioninc.com/), is

dedicated to developing scalable science based innovative solutions focused on health and risk

reduction. dfusion is staffed by public health and social and behavioral scientists with substantial

experience leveraging technology to bring science-based research to practice. dfusion works extensively

with expert partners, such as ETR, to work collaboratively to develop and commercialize innovative

commercial products in health and education.</p>
]]>
</string>
</resources>


